<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Iceland Travel Guide - Day Tours - Golden Circle - Northern Lights - Volcano Tours - South Shore - TripAdvisor Certificate Of Excellence - Family Company</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Iceland Travel Guide - Day Tours - Golden Circle - Northern Lights - Volcano Tours - South Shore - TripAdvisor Certificate Of Excellence - Family Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c), Volcano tours; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>itle>About Us - Family Company</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>The origins of the community of Grindavik can be traced back to Einar G. Einarsson, which set up shop there in 1897. During that time the town population was only around 360. Fishing has for centuries been a crucial element in the survival of Grindavik&amp;rsquo;s population. But fishing trips were often extremely dangerous. Men were frequently lost at sea and the catch wasn&amp;rsquo;t always stable. Today the tour operator &amp;ldquo;Volcano tours&amp;rdquo; has their office in Einar&amp;rsquo;s oldest shop house named &amp;ldquo;Flagghús&amp;rdquo; - &amp;ldquo;The flaghouse&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Please feel free to contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golden circle And South Shore Luxury Jeep Tour</title>
      <link>/tours/golden-circle-and-south-shore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tours/golden-circle-and-south-shore/</guid>
      <description>Your best choice, TWO TOURS IN ONE, especially for a short visit to Iceland by luxury jeep. We take you in small group to the most breath-taking places in Iceland in one day. From Reykjavik we drive through the South shore farmland with view of the volcano Eyjafjallajökull (E15). We touch blue-ice glacier,- waterfalls and walk on the black beach. Then we drive into the Golden circle with the our most famous waterfall “Gullfoss”, the real Geyser and Strokkur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northern Lights - Aurora Borealis Tour</title>
      <link>/tours/northern-lights-aurora-borealis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tours/northern-lights-aurora-borealis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Northern lights photographing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Small groups in luxury jeep ensure quietness to enjoy the northern lights experience.
We assist adjusting your camera for northern lights photographing if needed.
We find the world&amp;rsquo;s greatest places to view the northern lights with clear skies without light pollution.
If the Northern Lights are not seen in your first tour, we offer you to try once again for free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trips available nightly from the 1st Okt. until the end of March&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volcano Garden Reykjanes Peninsula</title>
      <link>/tours/volcano-garden-reykjanes-peninsula/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tours/volcano-garden-reykjanes-peninsula/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lava, Volcanoes, Hot-springs, Caving and Blue lagoon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local guided luxury jeep tour into historic lava fields and volcanoes. Seven colour hot springs, caving and the Blue lagoon. Reykjanes peninsula, the south west corner of Iceland, where the Atlantic rift rises from the ocean, with more than 100 volcano craters, 200 lava tubes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Blue lagoon is the most visited attraction in Iceland, a spa with warm geothermal under-ground seawater rich of silica.

It is possible to take bath in the Blue lagoon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volcano Tour Eyjafjallajokull (E15) View After The Eruption</title>
      <link>/tours/volcano-eyjafjallajokull-eruption/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tours/volcano-eyjafjallajokull-eruption/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Luxury jeep off road tour every day to one of Iceland&amp;rsquo;s most scenic spots, it is only accessible by specially equipped vehicles with experienced drivers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We do more than 30 unbridged river crossings when we drive close to the recently erupted volcano Eyjafjallajökull (E15) (AY-yah-fyad-la-ye kuh-tel). We go to the waterfall Seljalandsfoss that you can walk behind and step stones into the waterfall&amp;rsquo;s canyon Gljúfrabúi. We go to Gígjökull where the flood came in the eruption 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Óvissuferðir</title>
      <link>/ovissuferdir/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ovissuferdir/</guid>
      <description>Óvissuferð Hellaskoðun, hverasúpa, prestakaffi, leikir, hákarlahjall, danskennslu-harmonikkuball, kvöldverður o.fl. allt eftir þínum óskum. Við leggjum til vatnsvarða kulda­galla í allar okkar ferðir, einnig hjálma, ljós og hanska í hellaskoðun. Vinsamlega hafið samband og við gerum ykkur tilboð.
Eldfjallaferðir Ferðir um Reykjanesskagann þar er kynnt jarðfræði, jarðsaga, menning og minjar. Allur Reykjanesskaginn er undraheimur eldsumbrota. þar eru meira en 100 gígar og yfir 200 hraunhella. Einstök jarðfræðileg sérstaða Reykjaness er augljós þar sem úthafshryggurinn rís úr sæ gengur eftir Reykjanesskaganum.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>